<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fitness on SinLucidious</title>
    <link>/categories/fitness/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fitness on SinLucidious</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 - 2018, rlc4u; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/categories/fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Simply Said - Reducing Your Age</title>
      <link>/post/becoming-younger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/becoming-younger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death is a mystery. It is a scary darkness that is almost impossible to fanthom. If life is like a game, some people think that you would respawn in a different place, some people think that you replay the good bits of life in your brain over again, some people think that you enter a different dimension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/gWIi6Pytde8&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/br&gt;
The question begins as logical thinker, is there a way to cheat death? How can we extend our life way beyond the natural lifespan apart from uploading our conscience into the net or making use of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nbcnews.com/tech/innovation/company-will-freeze-your-dead-body-200-000-n562551&#34;&gt;cryopreservation&lt;/a&gt;. One possible way we could do this is by reducing our biological age to ensure that our system is always up and running together with some tissue regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High Intensity Interval Training (HIIT) 15mins/day - Strength/Resistance

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This will not only help to improve your fitness levels but help you to feel energetic through the day!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sleep 7-8 Hours a day

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sleep Deprivation can cause your life span to shorten by miles. Read more about it &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/features/10-results-sleep-loss#1&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; Use the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sleepcalculator.com/&#34;&gt;sleep calculator&lt;/a&gt; to help plan your sleep better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/post/losing-weight/&#34;&gt;Limit Toxins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pocketmindfulness.com/6-mindfulness-exercises-you-can-try-today/&#34;&gt;Healthy Mind - Meditation &amp;amp; Yoga&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Connection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always remember that to live a long life is to lead a life with a healthy mind and body. You can begin to see results in 2 weeks just by removing toxins from your body and building a healthly mind through mediation exercises. HIIT exercises with a restful sleep will work hand in hand to making you feel more positive in life and feeling younger, easing up the things that you were incapable of doing efficiently as before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simply Said - Weight Loss</title>
      <link>/post/losing-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/losing-weight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Losing weight can be painful, may seem impossible, counting calories can it exhausting. Been there, done that, backfired and crashed at. I proceeded to explore betters ways to lose weight, below includes some of the measures that I have found to work to effectively lose weight without losing your life and sense of self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Losing weight does not neccessarily means it is about going on a diet that causes you immense emotional pain. To help increase your metabolism, you can seek to use 2 types of method, either by drinking honey cinnamon water or a ginger lemon tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/cinnamon.jpg&#34; class=&#34;img-responsive center-block&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;preparations-include&#34;&gt;Preparations include&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp of Honey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp of Ceylon Cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;250ml of Hot Water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stir well, allow it to rest for 10 minutes and proceed to drink in the morning just after you wake up.
+ Ginger Lemon Tea&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;/images/ginger.jpg&#34; class=&#34;img-responsive center-block&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;preparations-include-1&#34;&gt;Preparations include&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simmer Ginger with Water for 30 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add Lemon Slices
Stir well, simmer for 20 minutes and proceed to drink after
You can read more about the benefits of honey, the differences between Cassia &amp;amp; Ceylon Cinnamon by clicking on the keywords.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these will help in aiding you by incrasing your metabolism to allow fats to be burn faster and easier. To further increase your weight loss process and helping to keep your body in a better condition, proceed to lift weights/ perform resistance training up to 3 times/ week. Its training only can be done as between 15-45 minutes. Refer to &lt;a href=&#34;http://darebee.com/&#34;&gt;Darebee&lt;/a&gt; for training programmes in which you can follow especially the workout cards.
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use raw organic honey with no sugars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For every 1 cup of water : (1 Tbsp of Honey, &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Tbsp of Ceylon Cinnamon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep carbohydrates and sugar intake to a minimum level. &lt;strong&gt;Note: Minimum not None&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>