<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hugo Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hugo Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Love Corona</title>
      <link>/post/corona/love4corona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/corona/love4corona/</guid>
      <description>Sample Corona Projects Before I begin, I thought I should start out by showing you some screenshots of the application that I have created! Namely: Sleep Tight and The Daily Dose.
What Do I Use Corona For? Currently, I primarily use Corona SDK for Business Mobile Application in which I publish onto the Google Play Store.
Is Corona Worth Learning? Currently Corona SDK is primarily used with Lua Programming Language which is easy to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo CI</title>
      <link>/post/dev-ops/hugoci/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dev-ops/hugoci/</guid>
      <description>Sneak Preview Today&amp;rsquo;s Topic will be all about Continuous Integration for Hugo Deployment! Click on the link to find out more but in a nutshell, it is a pretty neat tool for hosting a static website! The thing is that now that you are done creating your website with Hugo tool in localhost. You are ready to let it run public for the whole wide world to know! After browsing tutorials after tutorials and scanning through providers, i realized that hosting providers are definitely not the way to go and to keep cost low, I have decided to use Amazon S3 Storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps</title>
      <link>/post/dev-ops/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dev-ops/devops/</guid>
      <description>Behold Automation at it&amp;rsquo;s Finest Today&amp;rsquo;s Topic will be all about Continous Integration! Let&amp;rsquo;s Imagine this scenario, right now you are done with creating an awesome service that is capable of crawling the whole wide web or doing an e-commerce store. The problem now is that, you have to generate your own api blueprints (documentation), you have to manually deploy it to the cloud, make use of kubenetes settings. What is there was a way to automate all this these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Infrastructure Deployment</title>
      <link>/post/dev-ops/china-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dev-ops/china-deployment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we will be exploring the way of deploying the current service infrasture that you have built locally to deploying it on a server in china via Alibaba Cloud aka Aliyun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitness &amp; Health - Reducing Your Age</title>
      <link>/post/fitness--health/reducing-your-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fitness--health/reducing-your-age/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death is a mystery. It is a scary darkness that is almost impossible to fanthom. If life is like a game, some people think that you would respawn in a different place, some people think that you replay the good bits of life in your brain over again, some people think that you enter a different dimension.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Hugo On AWS</title>
      <link>/post/dev-ops/deploy-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dev-ops/deploy-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, I have been using Web Hosting Hub with wordpress installed with it to run my website. I got my domain name from OpenSRS. I am quite happy with their services and support. However, It has come to the point that I am clearly paying too much for just hosting a blog which stood at about 13 bucks a month.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simply Said - Weight Loss</title>
      <link>/post/fitness--health/losing-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fitness--health/losing-weight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Losing weight can be painfu and may seem impossible for some others. Even something as simple as counting calories can be exhausting. Been there, done that, backfired and ruined. I proceeded to explore betters ways to lose weight, below includes some of the measures that I have chanced upon that helps you to lose weight without losing your life and sense of self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Types of Developers</title>
      <link>/post/dev-ops/developer-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dev-ops/developer-stack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to taking your first step into the world of development. When you hear the word &amp;ldquo;programmer&amp;rdquo;, what first comes to your mind? Are there different type of programmers? If they are, what kind of programmers are they?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>