<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hugo Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hugo Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Website Crawler</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/webcrawler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/webcrawler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are going to explore building a web scraper to mark a milestone in our progression towards learning GO. This exercise will be emphasizing on the skills that you should already be familiar with. It will cover skills such as:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Dose</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/dailydose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/dailydose/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis This app helps you to keep track of all your daily habits so you would never forget them. You will also be able to ensure if you have reached your optimal nutrition and vitamin which will help you maximize your weight loss goals.
★ No Ads ★ Ensure you have completed your daily regime to stay productive ★ Add, Remove Daily Tasks ★ Ability to check progression of daily tasks and nutrition requirement ★ Free on all devices!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fit4life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/fit4life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/fit4life/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Are you currently on the hunt for workout routines that could make a difference in your life? Look no further as Fit4Life provides you with anything you need to maximize your gains and become fit in the shortest time possible.
★ Optimized workouts that helps to maximize your gains ★ Short &amp;amp; Sweet workout routines that ends in less than 1 hour ★ Fit4Life is free on all devices!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Tight</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/sleeptight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/sleeptight/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis This app helps to calculate the best time for you to sleep and wake up based on your needs. Being lethargic in the morning will be a thing in the past! The more sleep cycle you sleep through, the more refreshed you will feel.
Sleep better and wake up ready to seize the day! Stay tuned for more upcoming features such as tracking your sleep, alarms and many more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>